Do you want subtitles for any video?
-=[ ai.OpenSubtitles.com ]=-
Right. let's sort the buyers
from the spyers.
the needy
from the greedy.
and those who trust me
from the ones who don't.
Because if you can't
see value here today.
you're not up here shopping.
you're up here shoplifting.
You see these goods?
Never seen daylight.
moonlight. Israelite
or Fanny
by the gaslight.
Take a bag.
Come on. take a bag.
I took a bag
home last night.
and it cost me a lot more than £10.
I can tell you.
Anyone like jewelry?
Look at that one there.
Handmade in Italy. hand stolen in Stepney.
It's as long as my arm.
I wish it was as long as something else.
Don't think 'cause these boxes
are sealed up they're empty.
The only man who sells empty boxes
is the undertaker.
And by the look of some of you
lot here today.
I'd make more money with me
measuring tape. Here. one price.
£10.
Did you say £10?
BACON: Are you deaf?
That's a bargain.
I'll take one.
Squeeze in if you can.
Left leg. right leg. your body will follow.
They call it walking.
You want one as well. darling?
You do. That's it.
they're waking up.
Treat the wife.
treat somebody else's wife.
It's a lot more fun
if you don't get caught.
Hold on. you
want one as well?
Okay. darling. show
me a bit of life then.
It's no good standing out there
like 1:00 half struck.
Buy them. you better buy them!
These are not stolen.
they just haven't been paid for.
And we can't get them again.
they've changed the bloody locks.
Here. one for you.
It's no good coming back later
when I've sold out.
"Too late. too late!"
will be the cry
when the man with
the bargains has passed you by.
And if you've got
no money on you now.
you'll be crying tears as big as
October cabbages.
Bacon. cozzers.
BACON: Shit.
(ROCK MUSIC PLAYING)
ALAN: Ed can hustle
a few quid here and there.
but his real talent lies in cards
and gambling with cards.
Bacon could see
that his days of selling
moody goods on street corners
are numbered.
It's time to move on
and he knows it.
TOM: And I'm 6'1 ".
that's perfect for my height. all right?
NICK: All right. you take a photo.
You're catching up with me. you are.
Look. what are you talking about?
I'm bloody skinny. pal.
Yeah. yeah. of course you are.
All right?
Nick the Greek.
always a pleasure.
Tom. what have
you been eating?
I've been telling him this...
Enough already.
You two. join
me in my office.
So. how much
is it then. Tom?
You know how
much it is. Nick.
And that includes
the amp. yeah?
No. that does
not include the amp.
Shit. Tom. I thought
it included the amp.
Well. it
doesn't.
I'll throw in one of these telephones
if you like.
but it does not
include the amp.
Very nice.
I hope it includes
the speakers.
It doesn't include
it doesn't
include the amp.
and it's not
supposed to include me
getting the hump
with your stupid questions.
Now you want it.
Nick. you buy it.
What else do I get
with it?
You get a gold-plated
Rolls-Royce.
as long as
you pay for it.
Don't know. Tom.
Seems expensive.
Seems? Well. this seems to be
a waste of my time.
That is 900 nicker in any shop
you're lucky enough to find one in.
and you're complaining
about 200?
What school of finance did
you study?
It's a deal. it's a steal.
It's the sale of the fucking century.
In fact. fuck it.
Nick. I think I'll keep it.
All right. all right.
keep your Alans on.
Here's a ton.
Jesus Christ.
You could choke a dozen donkeys on that.
And you're
haggling over £100?
What do you do
when you're not buying stereos. Nick?
Finance revolutions?
£100 is
still £100.
Not when the price is
£200. it's not.
And certainly not when you got
Liberia's deficit in your sky rocket.
Tighter than a duck's butt you are.
Now come on.
let me feel
the fiber of your fabric.
ALAN: The skinny one is Tom.
and he's the entrepreneur
of the bunch.
He's got a couple of dirty little fingers
in a couple of dirty little pies.
Nick. here. however.
has made it his business
to have all 20 fat
little fingers and toes
in every dirty bent
and stolen pie in London.
Between the two of them.
there ain't much you can't get ahold of.
(SNIFFS)
That's my 25
grand. it's all there.
It took me a long time to earn that.
so you treat it with respect.
What about the chef?
TOM: What have you come as?
Cupid. stupid.
That's the last time
I'm getting any more fruit off of you. Tom.
Do you call
that fresh?
There was more small.
hairy armored things
in your fruit
than there was fruit.
You should open a butcher's.
not a grocer's.
Well. if you will order stuff
from Katmandu.
don't be surprised
if it picks up a few tourists en route.
Anyway. enough
about that.
Where's the money?
Oi!
Keep your fingers
out of my soup.
ALAN: Soap is called Soap
because he likes to keep his hands clean
of any unlawfuI behavior.
He's proud of his job
and even more proud that it's legal.
He represents the more
sensible side of the four.
You sure you
can afford 25?
That depends on
how you look at it.
I can afford it as long as
I see it again. if that's what you mean.
Got the rest
from the fat man and Bacon?
Fat man. Bacon
and myself.
Looks like it's time to make
that call to Harry.
Who's this fat man
then. eh?
Eh?
Do you want
a sandwich. Bacon?
(TELEPHONE RINGING)
ALAN: It's not easy
to take a seat at this card table.
The amount of money involved
has to be 100 grand upwards.
and there's no
shortage of punters.
The man who decides whether
you can play or not is this man. Harry.
Or as some. including himself.
like to call him. Hatchet Harry.
You got it all?
100 grand.
Well. if you got it.
you got it.
Now. if you
don't mind...
What's this
Eddie like. then?
He's a fucking thief.
ALAN: Harry has a colleague.
a monster of a man. Barry the Baptist.
The Baptist got his name
by drowning people for Hatchet.
Are you gonna fucking pay?
Yeah. I'll pay!
How are you gonna fucking pay?
I'm gonna pay it.
ALAN: Barry makes sure the administrative side
of the business runs harmoniously.
The boy's got
a rare ability.
He seems to make
cards transparent.
He's got...
All right. all right.
so we can say he's good.
Oh. no. he's
better than good.
He's a fucking
liability.
Here. hold on.
What do you think of these?
We're selling
hundreds.
Very nice. Harry.
What's it for?
Oh. don't play innocent with me.
Bazza. Spanking.
(ROCK MUSIC PLAYING)
There's 25 from me.
Tom. Soap and yourself.
That's 100 grand
to the pound.
So why the fuck
are you counting it?
Because I like to.
So. a reasonable return
should be in the region of 120 grand.
That's for 25 grand invested.
going on previous experience.
Going on
optimism.
Whatever it's going on. it should be enough
to send you on a cooking course.
You're not funny. Tom.
You're fat.
And look as though you should be.
but you're not.
Fat? Who are you
calling... Jesus!
It's good in
here. isn't it?
Handy for the tube.
great electrics.
I can see why you
moved in.
Don't knock it.
it's cheap like the budgie.
And nobody wants
to live next to the people we live next to.
(CHUCKLING)
A bit anti-social to say the least.
What do
you mean?
He means they're thieving bastards.
I mean. when they're
not picking peanuts out of poop.
they rip off unfortunate
souls of their hard-earned drugs.
Not exactly thick.
these walls.
MAN: Nice work. John.
Get yourself a drink.
Is that it?
How many times
do I have to tell you. Plank?
You find us a job worth doing.
you'll find your share improving.
Now. have you got a problem
with that?
(REGGAE MUSIC PLAYING)
You know. Charles.
this gear is getting heavier.
(COUGHS)
I have a strong suspicion
we should've been rocket scientists
or Nobel Peace Prize
winners
or something.
Peace Prize?
Be lucky to find your penis for a piss
the amount you keep smoking.
(DOORBELL BUZZING)
Who the hell's that?
All right.
Willie?
Does it look
like I'm all right?
Take this.
I'm in danger of breaking sweat
at any second.
WINSTON: Charles. why
have we got that cage?
Security?
That's right.
security.
So what's the point in having it
if we're not gonna fucking use it?
Well. I would have used it. Winston.
but this is Willie.
And Willie
lives here.
Yes. Charles.
but you didn't know it was Willie
until you opened
the door. did you?
Chill. Winston.
It's me.
Charlie knows it's me.
What's the
problem?
The problem is.
Willie.
that Charles and yourself are not
the quickest of cats
at the best of times.
So just do as I say
and keep the
fucking cage locked!
What is that?
That's Gloria.
Yes. I know that's Gloria.
What's that?
Fertilizer.
You went out six hours ago to buy
a money counter.
and you come back with a semi-conscious Gloria
and a bag of fertilizer?
Alarm bells
are ringing. Willie.
We need fertilizer.
Winston.
We also need
a money counter.
This money's gotta be out
by Thursday.
I'm buggered if
I'm gonna count it.
And if you do have to buy
sodding fertilizer.
could you just
be a little more subtle?
What do
you mean?
We grow copious amounts of ganja.
yeah?
Yeah.
And you're carrying a wasted girl
and a bag of fertilizer.
You don't look like your average
horti-fucking-culturalist.
That's what
I mean. Willie.
(JAZZ MUSIC PLAYING)
How long's he been in there. Son?
About 20
minutes.
He's on
his own?
Yeah. just
carrying a bag.
All right. let's pay
him a little visit then. shall we?
ALAN: Big Chris settles
debts for Harry.
The only thing he cares
more about than an unsettled debt.
is his son and heir.
Little Chris.
(JAZZ MUSIC PLAYING)
Shh!
This is one of them
high-powered jobs. isn't it?
(GROANING)
Got some bad
news for you. John.
What the fuck...
You mind your language
in front of the boy.
Jesus Christ.
That includes
blasphemy as well.
Now tell me. John.
how can you be concentrating
on improving
this lovely tan.
and it is a lovely
tan by the way.
when you've got more pressing
priorities at hand?
Tell Harry...
I mean Mr. Harry.
I've been busy.
I'm nearly there.
Check his
locker. Son.
JOHN: I don't suppose
there's any chance
of you lifting this sun bed up. Chris.
is there?
He's not poor.
He's got over
a monkey here.
and that's just
in his wallet.
Fucking hell. John.
you always walk around
with that in your pocket?
Oi!
You use language like that again.
Son. you'll wish you hadn't.
Sorry. Dad.
Right. well. put the
rest of the stuff in that.
You can go home
in a plastic bag tonight. John.
You owe
what you owe.
and by the time
this tan's faded.
you wanna
have paid.
You never would
Who would
pay for shit?
Yeah. exactly.
I mean we ain't too certain...
Well. what the hell are you
doing here?
Why. what's up?
Let me guess.
My foot in your arse.
Game of cards?
Hatchet Harry?
You're supposed
to be getting your rest in. boy.
You playing
cards tonight. Son?
With Harry?
Don't be
silly. Dad.
I wouldn't have
anything to do with that.
HARRY: Where did he
get 100 grand?
He's got some
adhesive mates.
I mean they're
like brothers.
They've tossed up
between them.
And JD is his dad and owns
the whole property?
No mortgage.
no debts.
Lock. stock.
the fucking lot.
Don't you worry. Harry.
I've got it under control.
Good. You can get this
under control now.
It seems that Lord Appleton Smythe
has run out of money.
And these little
beauties are up for auction.
But I'm not paying
a quarter of a million quid for them.
if you know
what I mean. Barry.
Make sure we get everything
from inside the gun cabinet.
I don't wanna know
who you use.
as long as they're
not complete muppets.
And don't tell
them what they're worth. Barry.
(JAZZ MUSIC PLAYING)
Right. where
was we?
Shotguns? What.
like guns that fire shot?
You must be
the brains. then.
That's right. guns
that fire shots.
Make sure you bring
everything from inside the gun cabinet.
There'll be a load of old guns.
That's all I want.
Everything else
outside the cabinet.
you can keep.
It's yours.
Thank you very much.
There'd better be something
there for us.
It's a fucking
stately home.
Of course there'll
be something there.
DEAN: Like what?
Like fucking antiques.
Antiques?
What the fuck do we know about antiques?
We rob post offices.
And steal cars.
What the fuck do we know
about antiques. mate?
If it looks old. it's worth money.
Simple.
So stop fucking moaning
and rob the place.
So who's the guv?
Who are we doing this for?
You're doing it for me.
is all you need to know.
You know because
you need to know.
I see.
One of those
on-a-need-to-know-basis things. is it?
Like one of those
James Bond films.
Careful. remember who's giving you
this job.
Right. I'm off.
Call me when you're done.
Ta-ta.
Fucking Northern monkeys!
I hate these fucking
Southern fairies.
ALAN: Ed has been playing cards since
he could lift them up.
and he soon discovered
that he had a big advantage.
It's not that he's good
with cards or even good at counting them.
It's that he's good with reading
people's reactions. no matter how subtle.
And everybody has reactions.
(KNOCKING ON DOOR)
especially when it comes to money.
Invitations.
Invitations?
Yeah.
invitations.
You know. four pretty white pieces
of paper with your names on them?
Well. we've got 100.000
bits of paper
with the Queen's
head on them.
Will that do?
All right.
just you.
The others. they can
wait next door in Samoan Jo's.
Samoan Jo's?
You mean the pub?
Hold on...
Hold on to your fucking tongue.
and I will hold onto my patience.
okay. sonny?
No one in here tonight but card players.
and I do mean no one.
Evening. Frazer.
Don. Phil.
It's a bit dramatic.
isn't it?
Is this supposed
to be symbolic?
Apparently. it's
for security.
Yeah? I'd have brought me gloves
if I'd have known.
You must be Eddie.
JD's son.
You must be Harry.
Sorry. didn't know
your father.
Never mind. son.
You just might meet
him if you carry on like that.
Evening. Tanya.
been a while.
All right. Ed?
(SCREAMING)
Right. we call each other Kenny.
okay. Gary?
All right.
Kenny.
You gonna put your stocking on.
or what?
I've just spent
220 quid on me hair.
If you think I'm pulling a stocking
over it.
you're very
much mistaken.
You're gonna
have to put something on.
This is three card brag.
gentlemen.
That means three
three's are the highest.
then three aces.
then running down accordingly.
Then it's a running flush. a run.
a flush and then a pair.
An open man can't
see a blind man.
and it will cost you
twice the ante to see your opponent.
Now don't fuck around. fellas.
You all know the rules.
and you know
I won't stand for it.
(CLOCK CHIMING)
(SOFTLY) What are you doing?
Put that back.
We're here
to rob the guns.
Put it back.
It's crap anyway.
Come on.
Come in.
(CHATTERING ON TV)
What sort of
pub is this. then?
It's a Samoan pub.
What's that?
It's a cocktail.
You asked for a cocktail.
No. I asked you
to give me a refreshing drink.
I wasn't expecting
a fucking rain forest.
You could fall
in love with an orangutan in that.
You want a pint.
go to the pub.
I thought this
was a pub.
It's a Samoan pub.
Well. whatever it is. can you get
your man to turn the TV down?
You can ask him if you like.
If I was you. I'd leave him well alone.
Here. get rid of that.
Bring us a Diet Coke.
Excuse me. can you
turn that TV down?
No.
(ALL WHOOPING)
(GROANING)
DEAN:
Whoa. whoa. Kenny!
What are you doing?
I am trying to find
out where they keep their money!
You twat. can't you
see these people have got no money?
They can't even
afford new furniture.
We've got the guns.
What's the matter with you?
Every time we do a job.
you have to go burning people's feet.
What's wrong with you?
You wanna be more careful.
old fella.
You very nearly took
my man's head clean off with that.
You all right.
Kenny?
10 grand. blind.
20 grand. open.
Deep end. eh?
Fold.
BARRY: Gotcha.
20 grand. open.
I'll fold.
Don't go spending
that all at once. boy.
(CELL PHONE RINGING)
Oh. bloody hell.
What?
I thought you said there'd be no staff.
Barry.
Did you get
those guns?
You wanna see
what they did to poor Gary?
Gary. Gary.
I said. did you
get those guns?
Yes! We got them!
Good. I'll speak
to you later.
Gary. if you can hear me.
get back in the car now. mate. okay?
Barry. Barry.
Fucking Southern shandy-drinking
bastard! Gary!
(ROCK AND ROLL MUSIC PLAYING)
Give me my money!
Give me back my money.
you fucking snake!
You give me
my money!
Give me back my money!
Give it back!
Wankers!
Come on. you.
Not now. please. Not now.
Oh. you fucking bastard.
(EXCLAIMING)
You bastard.
Oh. my good God.
We'll take you
to the cleaners.
20 grand. open.
£30.000.
Back to you
already. Eddie.
50 grand.
80 grand.
100 grand.
Whoa! Whoa! Whoa!
Look. fellas. I know...
I know you're not in.
Which means no one cares
what you know.
250.
That's quite a raise.
That's 150 on my 100.
Yeah. and is there anything else
you wanna say?
As you know.
this puts us in an awkward position.
I don't have enough
to continue.
We will have to see
both your cards
if no one loans Eddie
the money to continue.
It's a loan or we
see both your cards.
I will.
You will what?
I will loan you
the money.
No. I think I'd rather
just turn them over.
I'm not interested
in what you would rather.
I wanna keep going.
I'm also offering
you the money.
So we don't have to turn them over.
because you can borrow.
I need 250 grand.
No. you need
500 grand to see me.
That's if I
want to see you.
Well. you're gonna have a problem
carrying on. ain't you?
I'll see you.
Okay. before
I loan you this
I expect.
if you lose. of course.
my money back within a week.
Crystal?
That's Sunday.
okay?
Is that it?
Now let's see
his fucking cards.
(ROCK MUSIC PLAYING)
(RETCHING)
Hello. boy.
Feeling a bit poorly?
I know your friends
are responsible
for most
of the cash.
So. I'm gonna
give you one week to find it.
Otherwise. I will
take a finger
off each of you
and your friends' hands
for every day that passes
without payment.
And then when
you run out of digits.
your dad's bar.
and who knows what then.
All right. my son?
This doesn't
look good.
ALAN: He then
proceeded to explain
the unfortunate position
they were in.
Harry was going to start
sizing up all their fingers in a week.
because he knew there was no way
Ed could settle that debt on his own.
Harry saw it as their money on the table.
so it was also their debt off the table.
Ed would hate admit it.
but he could have kissed
the old bastard for that.
If he said he wanted to settle the debt
on his own. it would have been a lie.
Now. I wish to Christ he would have
let me settle the debt on my own.
I'm gonna
kill him!
Stop fucking
about. Tom.
and think about what we're gonna do.
Now sit down.
What's all the
fuss about Harry?
Why don't we just
boycott the payment?
Let me tell you
about Hatchet Harry.
BACON: Once there was
this geezer called Smithy Robinson
who worked for Harry.
but it was rumored
that he was on the take.
Harry's invited Smithy round
for an explanation.
Smithy didn't do a very good job.
Within a minute.
Harry's lost his rag.
reached out for the nearest thing at hand.
which happened to
be a 15-inch black rubber cock.
He then proceeded to batter poor Smithy
to death with it.
Now that was seen
as a pleasant way to go.
Hence. Hatchet Harry
is a man you pay if you owe.
Don't worry.
I'll think of something.
(UPBEAT MUSIC PLAYING)
"Golf. The best way to spoil a
good walk".
Winston Churchill
said that.
I say it's a
dog-eat-dog world.
and I've got bigger
teeth than you two.
(GORDON GRUNTING)
I think our friend
is trying to tell us something.
Perhaps not. Perhaps I should
take another swing just to make sure.
Give me a five iron.
John.
Certainly.
Dog.
Now. keep still.
Yes. Gordon. is there
something you'd like to tell us?
It's in
the fireplace.
Shut it.
you idiot!
Yes. Gordon.
you were saying?
It's in the fireplace. Just pull it out.
It's in the bottom.
It's in the fireplace. Plank.
Just pull it out. It's in the bottom.
Oh. Dog. I think you want to have
a look at this.
You gonna
let me down now?
DOG: No.
I'm not finished
with you yet.
Steel.
Help. help.
help!
Oh. Dog.
WOMAN ON TV: It's all up
to you. audience.
You have to decide.
yes. you have to decide
(DOORBELL BUZZING)
who the winner is going to be.
Who the hell's that?
It's only 12:00.
Use the cage.
that's what it's there for.
Who is it?
We have got security for a reason.
Willie.
Chill. Winston.
It's only Plank.
This weed's getting quite a rep.
you know. fellas.
All right?
Easy. Jesus!
Never saw you there.
Hello. love.
Enjoying yourself?
Is she compos?
What do you think?
Boo!
PLANK: Fuck me.
Clean that up.
Charles.
Sod you. You
clean it up.
Sorry. fellas. but that stupid cow
scared the fucking life out of me!
Never mind.
Can you just sit down?
Stay out
of the way?
Look. how much
is it you want?
I'm after a
half weight.
Right. well.
that's £1.500 then.
Pass the scales.
Willie.
Give us
some gear. J.
Any chance of actually seeing
the money?
The odds
are 100-to-one.
All as we
need is 5 grand.
I'd rather put my money
on a three-legged rocking horse.
The odds are 100-to-one
for a good reason. Bacon.
You won't win.
Where's Eddie?
Where do
you think?
The bottom of a bottle.
And has been for two days.
It's hit
him hard.
Yeah. it's hit us all hard.
Yeah. but he's got to tell his dad he's
about to lose his bar.
Listen to this one.
You open up a company
called Arse Ticklers Faggots Fan Club.
You what?
You take out an advert
in the back page of some gay mag.
advertising the latest in
arse-intruding dildos.
You sell it with.
I don't know.
"Does what no other
dildo can do until now.
"The latest and
greatest in sexual technology.
"Guaranteed results or your money back".
All that bollocks.
Now these dills
cost 25 quid a pop.
That's a snip for the amount of pleasure
they're gonna give the recipients.
But they send their
checks to the other company name.
nothing offensive. Bobbie's Bits.
or something. for 25 quid.
You take that 25 quid.
you stick it in the bank until it clears.
Now this is
the smart bit.
You send back the check for £25 from
the other company name.
Arse Ticklers Faggots Fan Club.
saying.
"We're sorry. and we couldn't get
the supplies from America.
"because they've
run out of stock. "
Now you see how
many people cash that check.
Not a single soul.
Because who wants
their bank manager to know
they tickle arse when they're not
paying in checks?
So how long do you have to wait till
you see the return?
Probably no more
than four weeks.
A month?
So what fucking good
is that if we need it in six...
No. five days.
Well. it's still
a good idea.
He may know we smoke a lot and
burn a bit of profit.
but he can't have any idea how much hard
currency we've accumulated.
I don't know.
Do you know?
We can just slice
it off the top.
WINSTON: You guys
gotta realize who this chap is.
He might look a bit silly.
but he's a fucking lunatic.
And if he gets the slightest inkling we're
not throwing straight dice.
then you and me are gonna know what
the sharp side of a kebab knife feels like.
So you know
these geezers well?
PLANK: Well enough.
I've been buying gear
off one of them for a couple of years.
So. what are
they like then?
Poofs. Nothing heavy.
Four public schoolboys. Soft as shite.
PLANK: They ponce around in funny hippy
clothes all day. talking bollocks.
They're just good at growing weed.
that's all.
Business has got bigger
than what they can keep up with.
DOG: Well. they can't all be stupid.
can they?
Think about it. They've got a container
load of cash in shoeboxes.
They're selling
class-A gear.
Don't you think there
might be someone sensible involved?
What about security?
PLANK: There's one steel gate as you go in.
but they never lock it.
What do you mean.
never lock it?
What have they
got it there for then?
I must have been there 50 times.
It's never locked.
They're not suspicious.
Everyone who
goes there's a toff.
They're all into
that karma crap.
"If I don't harm nobody.
nobody harms me" stuff.
No way they
can get back to you?
Even if they could. they'd be too shit scared.
I'm a geezer.
They got no muscle.
Gutless faggots.
Fancy one?
What's all the flapping about?
You told the
old man yet?
Hoping I
won't need to.
I've got a plan.
Now listen carefully.
Hello. boys.
Harry.
Do you want
a drink?
Hello. my son.
do you want a lolly?
Piss off.
you nonce.
Oi! Watch it.
No thanks. Harry.
We're both all right.
Nice shooter.
Yeah. one
of a pair.
Holland & Holland.
Do you want to hold it?
No. not my thing.
Thanks. Harry.
Business good?
I imagine that's why I'm here.
Four young fellas got in deeper than
they could handle.
They owe me half
a million pound.
LITTLE CHRIS:
How much?
Half a million.
I'm game.
Me. too.
Oh. God.
Right.
We hit them
as soon as they come back.
We'll be prepared.
waiting.
And they're armed.
What was that?
Armed?
What do you mean. armed?
Armed with what?
Bad breath. colorful language.
feather duster...
What do you think
they're gonna be armed with?
Guns. you tit.
Guns? You never
said anything about guns.
A minute ago this was the safest job
in the world.
Now it's turning
into a bad day in Bosnia.
Soap. stop being such a mincer.
I've thought
about that and...
And what exactly?
And all we have to
do is find out who's carrying them.
Carrying them? Well. they could all
be carrying them for what we know.
No. Only one of them carries
them going to the job.
So I assume the
same one will be carrying them
when they come back
from the job.
Oh. you assume.
do you?
And what do they say about assumption
being the brother of all fuck-ups?
It's the mother
of all fuck-ups. stupid.
Well. brother. mother.
any other sucker.
it don't make
any difference.
They're still fucking guns.
and they still fire fucking bullets.
Soap. if you
have a better idea
how to get £500.000 in the next few days.
let us know.
In the meantime. Tom. you talk
to Nick the Bubble about shifting the weed.
Weed?
No. it's not normal weed.
It's some
fucked-up-skunk. class-A.
I-can't-think-let-alone-move
shit.
Doesn't sound
very good me.
No. neither me.
But it depends what flicks your switch.
And the light is on
and burning brightly for the masses.
Anyway. do you
know anyone?
I know a man. yes.
Rory Breaker.
Not that madman
with an Afro?
I don't want anything
to do with him.
You won't have to.
Just get me a sample.
No can do.
What's that?
A place near Katmandu?
Meet me
halfway. mate.
Look. it's all
completely chicken soup.
It's what?
It's kosher as Christmas.
Jews don't celebrate
Christmas. Tom.
Yeah. well. never mind that.
I'm gonna need some artillery. too.
Couple of
sawn-off shotguns.
This is a bit heavy.
This is London. not the Lebanon.
Who do you
think I am?
I think you're
Nick the Greek.
Hold those two.
I don't normally have
anything to do with weed. Nick.
But if it is
what he says it is.
I'll take it off him
for 3.5 grand a key.
That is if it is
what he says it is.
I don't want to
see it after a sample.
touch it after a sample.
I'll leave you in
the capable hands of Nathan here.
He'll sort out
the details.
But just let me
tell you one thing.
If the milk turns out to
be sour.
I ain't the kind
of pussy to drink it.
Do you know
what I mean?
(GLASS SHATTERING)
Rory Breaker.
Rory? Yeah.
I know Rory.
He's not to
be underestimated.
He's a funny looking fucker.
I know.
But you've got to look past
the hair and the cute cuddly thing.
It's all a
deceptive facade.
A few nights ago.
Rory's Roger iron rusted.
He's gone down the Battle Cruiser
to watch the end of a football game.
No one's watching the custard.
so he switches the channel over.
A fat geezer's
north opens.
And he wanders up
and turns the liza over.
"Now fuck off
and watch it somewhere else".
Rory knows claret is imminent. but
doesn't wanna miss the end of the game.
So calm as a coma.
picks up a fire extinguisher.
walks straight past
the jam rolls who are ready for action
and plonks it
outside the entrance.
He then orders an Aristotle of
the most ping-pong tiddly in the nuclear sub
and switches
back to his footer.
"That's fucking it."
says the geezer.
"That's fucking what?"
says Rory.
And he gobs out a
mouthful of booze covering Fatty.
He flicks a flaming
match into his bird's nest.
and the geezer's lit up
like a leaking gas pipe.
Rory. unfazed. turns back to his game.
His team's won. too.
Four-nil.
(ROCK MUSIC PLAYING)
Oi!
Is your hair supposed to look
like that?
All right.
short stuff?
Never mind
"short stuff. "
Listen. the next time we do
a job like this.
we're gonna want
more money. Barry.
Or we're going back
to post offices and cars. Fuck that.
Where's the
others?
There was
no others.
Stop fucking around.
The others. the old ones.
I don't know
what you mean.
There were two old guns
there.
Where are
they now?
Not in the cabinet.
there wasn't.
There was a couple of old hammer-lock
muskets the butler was carrying.
But they were ours.
we sold them.
Well. you better unsell them.
sharpish.
We had to sell them.
We needed the money!
I'm not
fucking interested!
If you don't want to be counting the fingers
you haven't got
I suggest you get those guns.
quick!
Jesus.
If I pick them up.
will they stay in one piece?
Where'd you
get them?
I got contacts.
Listen. Tom.
you point them at me.
I'll shit myself
or do whatever you say to do.
Either way you
get the desired effect.
Oh. they look
very nice. I agree.
but they're lackingin criminal credibility.
ain't they?
I might get laughed at.
How much do
you want for these muskets?
£700 each.
What's that?
A pound for every year they've been about?
I know they're antiques.
but I ain't paying antique prices.
They're a bit long.
ain't they?
Sawn-offs are out.
People want a bit more range these days.
Range?
I don't want to blow
the arse out of this country. granted.
But I don't want anyone
blowing a raspberry at me. either.
I want to look
fucking mean.
Of course
you'll look mean.
You'll look
really scary.
Anyway. enough
about that.
What about this geezer
who sells drugs?
Rory Breaker's
standing by.
You stand to make a lot of money.
tubby Tommy.
BIG CHRIS: I understand
if this has come as a bit of a shock.
but let me tell you how this can be
resolved by you. the good father.
Go on.
He likes your bar.
Yes?
He wants your bar.
And?
Do you want me
to draw you a picture?
Look. that boy doesn't
know his arsehole from his ear hole.
This is my bar.
It's got nothing to do with him.
What. and I care?
Remember. you do have
the luxurious advantage
of being able to
sustain your son's life.
And you do have a reputation.
so I'll choose my words very carefully.
You tell Harry
to go fuck himself.
Now.
I'll put that down to shock.
Only once.
Only once can I
or shall I let you get away with that.
Your son's got three
days to find half a mil.
But make up your mind
which you prefer.
your bar or your son.
DOG: Plank goes in first.
There's a cage.
but it's never locked.
DOG: Is it. Plank?
Never.
DOG: It don't wanna be.
All right. once he's got himself set.
he gets the rest of us in.
(FEEDBACK SCREECHING)
Now we get nasty with a couple of them.
Shit them up.
gag them. whatever.
Now these wankers
shouldn't give us any problems.
But like any cowboys.
there'll be a few tools lying around.
When the job's done.
we come straight back here and unload.
And Robert's
your father's brother.
Everyone savvy?
ALL: Sweet.
Have a look at these.
And what are we
supposed do with these?
Put them on
your head. stupid.
Christ.
If you think I'm gonna turn up
there clean-shaven and greet them
with a grin on my face.
you got another thing coming.
Now these fellas.
they're your neighbors.
I thought it might be
a good idea to disguise ourselves a little.
Right. Yeah. good thinking. Soap.
Well done.
I brought
weapons as well.
Weapons? What do
you mean. weapons?
(CLEARS THROAT)
These.
(EXCLAIMING) Jesus.
Let's keep them
covered up. eh?
Couldn't you have
got anything a bit bigger?
What. like that?
What do you think?
I think you
need help.
Bar steward. can we have
a couple of drinks. please?
Have you seen your dad?
Hatchet sent one of his men around.
Oh. shit. When?
Crazy...
Where did you get these?
A fucking museum?
Nick the Greek.
How much
did you part with?
£700 for
the pair.
Drachmas. I hope.
I'd feel safer
with a chicken drumstick.
These are gonna
do more harm than good.
Jesus. Tom.
do these work?
Don't know.
Look nice though. don't they?
I rather like them.
That's top of the list of priorities.
that is.
EDDIE: Ladies.
back to more important issues.
if you don't mind.
We have only got two real guns.
Apparently.
that's what they are.
So we find a good place to
hide next door.
we wait till it sounds like
the right time.
then we
jack-in-the-box.
look nasty and stuff.
cocoon them in gaffer tape.
nick their van. swap the gear into the new van
and bring it all back here.
As long as we're all out of our hiding
places quickly.
it's the last thing they're
gonna expect.
Oh. and if Tom
or anyone else for that matter
feels like giving
them a bit of a kicking.
I'm sure it won't
do any harm.
Yeah. little bit
of pain never hurt anybody.
if you know
what I mean.
Also. I think knives
are a good idea.
Big. fuck-off.
shiny ones.
Ones that look like they could
skin a crocodile.
Knives are good
because they don't make any noise.
And the less
noise they make.
the more likely we are to
use them.
Shit them right up.
Makes it look
like we're serious.
Guns for show.
knives for a pro.
Soap. is there something we should
know about you?
I'm not sure what's more worrying.
the job
or your past.
Come on. girls.
Where the fuck are they going?
Shift a piano?
I thought this was meant
to be a robbery.
Where did they get those outfits?
BOTH: Not a
bad idea. that.
All right. it's Plank.
Is Willie there?
No. I'm afraid he's not.
He's out at the moment.
PLANK: Perhaps
you can help.
Well. perhaps I can't. Plank.
if you know what I mean.
Look. If you could just
open the door.
so I could talk
without shouting.
J: I can't help
you. Plank.
I think you'll find it is in
your interest.
Hold on. okay?
Look. Willie.
it's Plank outside for you.
He says it's
in our interest.
Listen. I don't care if it's
King-fucking-Kong!
He's not coming in here.
not today.
Hold on. We are in business.
and correct me if I'm wrong.
but that
is business.
Corrected. That's a walking accident that
we can do without.
Jesus. he's okay.
He knows only to buy weights now.
We're looking at
at least a couple of thou.
What do you
think. Winston?
Willie. this is the last time.
all right?
But you and the money
are going out the back.
If he knows you're here.
he'll be all day.
Now just clear this
shit up.
What. now?
Yes. Now!
Just get rid
of him quick.
All right.
just coming.
What the fuck
is he doing?
Come on. I can't wait out
here all day.
J: All right.
just coming.
I thought you was
gonna leave me out there all day.
I didn't know you
were a removals man. Plank.
Lives and learns.
don't you?
You keep the gates locked
now. do you?
Sorry. gotta do business
like this now.
Can't be too careful
these days.
I know. Shut it!
You say a fucking word.
the right ear goes.
Another one.
then your left.
What are you
doing. Plank?
What do you
think I'm doing?
Hang on. what
are you doing?
Unlock the gate. All right.
I said unlock the fucking gate!
That's it!
Go. go. go! Fucking move!
What the fuck's
going on?
Just hang on.
I've got the keys.
The gate's locked!
I don't believe the fucking gate's locked!
What have you
done to Fauntleroy?
I didn't touch him.
He just passed out.
Don't just stand there.
Get that fucking door shut.
You want the
world to see us?
(MEN ARGUING)
What's going
on down there?
Shit.
Charles. get
the rifle out.
We're being fucked.
It must be
this one.
Hold that gun.
Plank. give me the keys.
Give me the keys. Plank.
Don't point it at me.
bollocks. point it in there.
DOG: Planks of wood.
I'm working with fucking planks of wood.
Shit.
What the fuck is that?
What the fuck's that?
It's me Bren gun.
Don't you think you could have brought
something a little bit more practical?
Don't none of you slags move.
I'll kill the fucking lot of you!
Who are you gonna kill. Plank?
There's no one fucking there.
(SCREAMS)
They fucking
shot me.
Well. shoot
them back.
Jesus. Plank.
Couldn't you have got smokeless cartridges?
I can't see a bloody thing.
(GROANS)
Shit.
I've been shot.
I don't fucking believe this.
Could everyone
stop getting shot?
DOG: John. sit down
and patch yourself up.
You tart. it's
a fucking air rifle.
What the fuck
was that?
Well. that
was the Bren gun.
If you fire
that gun again.
you're a dead man.
Understand? Dead.
No ifs. no buts.
you're a fucking dead man!
All right.
all right.
I've got the bollock ache with this.
Where's me fucking gun?
All right. now that I've got
your attention.
firstly I'm gonna
blow his toes off.
(GUN FIRING)
(WHISPERING) Shit.
DOG: There go his toes.
Now if you want
me out of here in five minutes flat.
open the
fucking gate.
'cause I'm gonna
blow his leg off.
They're gonna fucking kill us
if we do. man.
Poor J will certainly get it if we don't.
He's serious.
I'm losing patience.
Hurry up. girls.
WINSTON: It's all right.
All fucking right.
Willie. he doesn't know
you're here. Just...
Sort something out.
And all your friends.
there's a good lad.
There's only
three of us here.
I don't believe you.
Fuck it. I'm gonna blow his leg off.
I mean it.
It's only
three of us.
DOG: Plank?
Yeah. One
of them is out.
Now open
the gate.
(SIGHS)
(GROANING)
Up. up. up.
There's a good lad.
(ROCK MUSIC PLAYING)
John. get
them tied up.
Plank. where's
the money?
There. In those
shoeboxes.
Where?
Out the back.
And the weed?
Point.
With what?
Your fucking
hands. now.
I'm tied up.
Well. nod your
head or something.
Check it out.
Plank. get Paul out of that van. lively.
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
(SCREAMS)
(GUN FIRING)
Knife.
I'm gonna cut him.
Make sure he knows he's dead.
How you doing. Mick?
How do you think I'm doing?
He's fucking nearly
chopped me arm off.
Jesus Christ.
Lenny. what the
fuck's been going on here?
Shut up. you idiot.
It's Hanukkah.
Well. don't just
stand there.
Have you got the bags?
Can you fit it all in?
It's a lot.
I can't get Epping Forest
in my van.
Can't? I don't
wanna hear "can't. "
Bollocks to can't.
You'll fit it all in
if you have to make two trips.
Bollocks.
You've got
a ticket already.
And if you don't move it.
we will move it for you.
I'll only
be a minute.
You've already
been 15.
Look.
Come and
have a look.
At what. exactly?
Well. the van's half full.
So?
So. all I've got
to do is fill it up.
put you in it...
What?
And I'm off.
Do you think you can carry more than
one bag this time?
I can't.
My neck. Dog.
How many more bags?
JOHN: Just a couple.
Mick. you dead yet?
I'll be all right once I've dealt with
that lanky prick.
DOG: Do it quietly.
It's time I say.
"Good night. nurse. "
(GUN CLICKING)
(SCREAMING)
Where the fuck
did she come from?
(PANTING)
That is it. Tie her up.
We're out of here.
What are you
doing. Ed?
Do you
want one?
No. I fucking don't.
You cannot make a cup of tea. Edward.
The entire British Empire was
built on cups of tea.
SOAP: Yeah. and look
what happened to that.
And if you think I'm going to war
without one. mate. you're mistaken.
Going to war
with what?
Have you forgotten
those guns. you dozy prat?
You won't get away
with this.
Paul. what's that?
It's a
traffic warden.
I can see it's a fucking
What's he doing
in the back of the van?
He was gonna
call the cozzers.
Fair enough.
we'll deal with him later.
How are
we doing. Tom?
Right as rain.
I'm just gonna
take care of the cabs.
Keep us posted.
All right. mate.
do you do airports?
Where the hell
are we gonna hide?
Don't complicate
things. Just hide.
We're on.
Cor. they weigh
a pound or two.
Shut up
and back up!
(WHISTLES)
Spin round.
big boy.
What the fuck?
Stay down.
Stay down!
Tie them up. tape them up.
hands and face.
On the floor!
Bend over
the fucking desk.
Keys. I want
keys. Now!
I'll find you.
Course you
will. sweetheart.
I'll find you.
What do you think this is.
fucking hide-and-seek?
That one.
Search that one.
Right. I'll see you in the van
when you've finished with handsome here.
Jesus. that wasn't too bad. was it?
When the bottle in my arse has contracted.
I'll let you know.
Bacon. see
what we've got.
Let's have
a butchers. eh?
We've hit
the jackpot. lads.
We've got God knows
how much of this stinking weed.
a shit load
of cash
and a
traffic warden.
What?
Jesus. Ed.
we got a traffic warden.
I think he's
still alive.
He's got claret
coming out of him somewhere.
What did they
want with a traffic warden?
I don't know.
but I don't think we need him.
Knock him out
and dump him at the lights.
Knock him out?
What do you mean. knock him out?
Knock him
out with what?
I don't know!
Use your imagination!
(GROANING)
Don't touch him up.
Knock him out!
I'll knock you
out in a minute.
Look. you want to knock
him out.
you knock
I fucking hate
traffic wardens.
It's about time you gave
my young friends a visit. Chris.
Tomorrow's the
day and mum's the word.
Now I can't have that.
can I. Baz?
No. Harry.
you can't.
I mean. it's
a liberty.
And I can't have
a liberty taken. can I. Chris?
No. Harry.
you can't.
I mean. it's enough to
give me the arsehole.
And I can't have
the arsehole. can I. boys?
BOTH: No. Harry. you can't.
EDDIE: Right. that's it.
We're done.
We're off.
Here. Ed.
Are you sure it's a good idea
taking this back to yours?
Well. it's the only place we
can take it.
and it's the last
place they're gonna look.
Anyway.
fuck it!
The battle is over
and the war is won.
Now. Tom.
You take this to Nick the Bubble.
then we get
rid of it quick.
It's skunk.
and it's as good as it gets.
All right.
we'll take it.
Half price.
I don't think
he'll like that.
You said 3.5 a key.
and you know that's a good price.
It was yesterday
I said three and a half.
and now it's today
if I'm not mistaken.
We'll take it
tomorrow. half price.
If he wants to
get rid of it quick.
he'll have
to take it.
Now look.
I've got a race coming up
in a minute.
so if you'd just be
kind enough to...
Lenny. take that round to Snow White
and the three little chemists.
They should
have a gander of that.
I want a
second opinion.
LENNY: Hang on a minute. Nathan.
Something stinks.
NATHAN: Yeah. your
fucking aftershave.
LENNY: Fuck you.
funny man.
For God's sake.
Help me.
I'm in pain.
I'm in so much pain! Jesus.
Go in slowly.
Nathan.
Fuck you. funny
man. you go first.
Just get the fuck
in there. will you?
I want this house searched
for bugs.
I mean.
I want it stripped.
Where's the
point in that?
Even if there was a bug.
they'd have taken it with them.
It's a bit late for you to start
thinking. John.
If it's a possibility.
that's good enough for me.
And when you've
stripped this place.
I want every slag this side of Ceylon
pulled in and tortured badly.
I want to know
who's responsible for this.
Otherwise. I'm gonna
hold you responsible.
EDDIE: Not a bad day.
That pile takes
care of Harry.
What's left
over?
Give me half
a chance to count it.
What about
this gear then. eh?
What. you want
a toke on that?
No. I don't think
I want any of that horrible shit.
Can we lock up
and get drunk now. please?
We shot one of them
in the throat.
What do you
want. a medal?
I'll shoot you in the fucking throat
if I don't get my ganja back.
RORY: The one you shot.
is he still in there now?
No. it was
another one.
That's more like it.
Where is he?
Well. they
took him with.
No. he's
still alive.
What did you shoot him with?
An air gun?
Look. we grow weed.
We're not mercenaries.
You don't say.
Who could it be?
Where do
we start. Rory?
Mr. Breaker.
Today my name
is Mr. Breaker.
You think this is
a coincidence?
This white shite
steals my things
and thinks that he
can sell it back to me!
He's got less brains than you.
Lenny!
Get Nick.
the greasy wop...
Greek bastard round here now.
If he's still stupid enough to be
on this planet.
(ROCK SONG PLAYING)
Your stupidity might be
your one saving grace.
Uh?
Don't "uh" me.
Greek boy!
How is it your fucking stupid.
soon-to-be-dead friends
thought that they might be able to
steal my cannabis.
and then sell it
back to me?
Is this a
declaration of war?
Is this some white cunt's joke that
black cunts don't get?
'Cause I'm not fucking laughing.
Nicolas!
I know you couldn't
have known my position.
'cause you're not that stupid
that if you did.
you wouldn't have
turned up here scratching your arse
with that. "What's
going on here" look
slapped all over
your Chevy Chase.
But what you do know
is where these people live.
If you hold back
anything. I'll kill you.
If you bend the truth.
or I think you're bending the truth.
I'll kill you.
If you forget anything.
In fact. you're gonna have to work
very hard to stay alive. Nick.
Now. do you understand
everything I've said?
Because if you don't.
I'll kill you.
Now. Mr. Bubble and Squeak.
you may enlighten me.
So we've got a bit of a problem.
ain't we?
Well. yeah.
Yeah. we do.
Yeah. yeah. we do.
In fact. it's a little bit more than
a little bit of a problem. isn't it?
On a scale of things.
you could say
it's the Mount fucking
Everest of problems.
And the reason it's such
a mon-fucking-strosity of a problem is.
you don't even got
a first idea who did this to us. have you?
Dog. we've been up all night.
It's no one from round here.
We've had them
all lined up against the wall.
If he was a toe-rag from out of manor.
we'd know.
We'd know.
You'd know?
You'd fucking know?
You wouldn't know
if it was the next door fucking neighbors!
Now get out there and find them!
I'm sick of the fucking sight of you!
Get out of my fucking sight!
You little shit!
Scarface.
I've watched
If you want to know how to do a drug deal.
you watch Scarface.
That really inspires confidence. that.
This guy
Rory Breaker...
Rory Breaker?
Psychotic black dwarf with an Afro?
That'll be the
same man. yes.
I heard about him.
He's a fucking lunatic.
Well. he can afford
to do the deal at the price we're selling.
It's not worth him giving us
any trouble.
because he knows
we'll be a pain in the arse.
and who needs
a pain in the arse?
I'll take a pain in
the arse for half-a-million quid.
You'd take a pain
in the arse for air miles.
Tom. the fatter you get.
the sadder you get.
Will you two
stop flirting for a minute?
After we pay Hatchet.
this deal puts us up
nearly £200.000
each.
That's not bad for a morning's work.
I think you'll agree.
So they had the cash.
And the puff.
Cheeky bastards.
Count it.
Shit. Dog. there's a lot.
Don't you want to do it next door?
We're not going next door till we've flayed
them dead men walking.
We'll count
it upstairs.
I don't want them
to see you fingering their money
when they walk through the door.
But. Dog. look...
Give us it here.
dozy bastard.
Check your guns.
Get yourselves well hid.
You wait till they get right
inside the door.
then you
give it to them.
Give me them shooters.
you can use your own.
(CELL PHONE RINGING)
Yeah?
That's no way
to answer the phone.
(EXCLAIMS) Is that
you. Dean?
No. it's
Lord fucking Lucan.
Who do you
think it is?
What can I
do for you?
You know those guns I sold you?
I need them back.
Not likely. I'm afraid.
I don't think I'll be seeing them again.
Look. I've got the money
to pay for them.
I'm sure you do.
but I don't think you understand.
I ain't gonna be seeing them or
the guns again.
Can't
get them.
If we can't get them.
we can't get them.
Well. you'll have
to fucking get them.
Look. we made the fucking deal
for everything inside the cabinet.
Inside-out-fucking-side.
I don't give a shit.
You get those guns.
because if you don't...
Oh. yeah.
Bazza. or what?
Have you heard
of Harry Lonsdale?
Otherwise known as "Hack you up with
a hatchet Harry?"
Well. this is
James Bond.
need-to-know time.
When you dance with the devil.
you wait for the song to stop.
Know what I mean?
I mean. find them.
torture them and kill them.
And bring back
what belongs to me.
Because if you don't.
your family's bang in trouble.
Who was that?
(SIGHS) That was
Harry Horrible Hatchet.
Jesus. I've
heard of him.
DEAN: We're in shit.
They were his fucking guns we sold.
We've got to find them.
Now. no fucking about now. Nick.
Where can I find those guns?
Six black cocks and a little white kitten
sitting on the side of the road.
We're gonna
do a proper decoration job.
I want the gray skies
of London illuminated.
I want that
house painted red.
(ALL LAUGHING)
All right.
There's this brass
standing on the corner. right.
Dwarf walks up
to her carrying a suitcase.
Winston. there. is gonna come along
and see if he recognizes any of them.
Now watch out
for these fellows.
They've got a bit
of an arsenal.
and they
don't mind using it.
And I'm taking
down her panties.
Now. does everyone
here know what they've got to do?
Yeah.
What the fuck
is going on?
(GUNS FIRING)
(GLASS SHATTERING)
You got something here for me.
have you?
Come on.
chop-chop.
Thank you very much.
He's got the guns.
Go ahead. you get them.
Why me?
You're supposed
to be the hard case...
You go and get the guns!
I drive the car!
Good boy.
Oh. get the
fucking guns!
I'm not going
to get the fucking guns!
You get the
fucking guns!
You fucking...
(MOCKING LOUDLY)
All right. wrap
them guns up.
Count the money.
Put your
seat belt on.
GARY: Fucking guns!
We've got to get the fucking guns.
or we're dead!
(STARTING CAR)
So I made sure
I fucked the one that was coughing.
(ALL LAUGHING)
Get out of the car.
you yuppy fucker!
(DOG SHRIEKING)
He's the one
we shot in the neck.
Is that right.
Mr. Botanical?
(GUNS FIRING)
(EXCLAIMING) Jesus.
I don't believe this.
What the fuck has happened here?
Jesus.
The money.
The gear.
This is fucked.
No money.
No weed.
It's all been replaced
by a pile of corpses.
All right.
don't panic.
Let's think
about this.
No. fuck that.
You can think about it.
I am panicking and I'm off.
How did you get your hands
on these then?
The boys
had them.
I know you like
these sort of things.
Wondered if
you wanted them.
Yeah. I'll have them.
Was it hard work
getting the money?
Not especially.
Upset a few
characters though.
You counted it?
Yeah. It's all there.
to the pound.
And they
were gonna pay?
Looks like it.
but who knows?
The opportunity
was there.
In my experience.
it's best to take that opportunity
if it's there.
Good work. Chris.
DEAN: We've got to
get those guns.
This is dangerous shit. Dean.
We don't even know who lives there.
Listen. I don't care
who lives there!
All's I know is that
it's preferable to death by Hatchet.
GARY: Fair enough.
Let's go.
I don't think
it's the right move.
It's either that.
the old boy's place and we lose a digit daily.
I'm gonna
phone him.
As if
he'll care.
He'll care all right.
That was supposed to be his money.
Whether he cares
about us or not is different.
Pass me the phone.
(PHONE RINGING)
Yeah?
That you. boy?
It's Ed. if that's
what you mean.
Pay day. isn't it?
Yeah. I wanted to
talk to you about that.
I'll bet you do.
I've got half-a-million
nickers sitting here.
which means some
poor sod doesn't.
You've been upsetting
a few people. boy.
But that really
isn't my concern. is it?
What does concern me
is the guns you had.
And I want to
talk to you about that.
So get your arse over here now.
and I do mean now.
Bastard! You
fucking bastard!
Fucking bastard!
(SCREAMS)
What the fuck
are you doing here?
Job well done.
We made a few quid out of that one.
Son?
Made a few quid.
did you?
Where's what
I want?
You all right
down there. mate?
Very fucking
funny.
Where's what
I want?
I've just left
it in the office.
We better go to the office
and get it then.
That's if you want your son to see
his next birthday.
Now chop-fucking-chop.
All right.
fair enough.
Where are
you going?
It's a 30-second drive
or a five-minute walk.
And I couldn't
have parked outside.
I'd have
got a ticket.
I suppose that don't
matter now. does it?
Just be careful.
Right.
You and me.
You and who?
You know where the door
handle is. Tom.
Oh. no.
not again!
That's it. I'm off.
Tom. that is
our bag.
Ed.
Hold on.
This is our bag.
That's it. we're off.
I'll see you in the car.
I'm gonna take these guns.
Tom. don't
fuck about!
I'll see you
in the car.
Tom.
It'll only take a minute.
What is going on?
I don't know.
But what I do know is there's no more Harry.
which means
there's no more debt.
And if there's no more debt.
there's no more problem.
And there's no problem with the neighbors.
because they're all dead.
And I think. if I
get this right.
we haven't done anything wrong.
and we're in the clear.
(TIRES SCREECHING)
Never ever
has anyone ever
been as fucking
rude to me
as you did!
Fucking bastard!
You all right.
mate?
Cheeky bastard.
ALAN: Now this was an embarrassing position
for Tom to be in.
But Chris had to
respect the fact
that he was holding what
appeared to be a pair of loaded shotguns.
And Tom had to respect
the fact that they were not loaded.
So. without anybody
losing too much face.
Tom left through a side door.
and Chris left with the money.
And everybody else
got arrested.
He's not
one of them.
(ROCK MUSIC PLAYING)
I think your dad would like a word
with you. Ed.
Where are the others?
They got out yesterday.
They're back at the bar.
All right. Dad?
I'm all right.
How about yourself?
Oh. I'm all right.
Could do with
a drink. though.
All in good time.
all in good time.
So you in the clear?
More importantly. am I?
It appears so.
Appears?
You'll have to do better
than fucking appears. my friend.
Well. everybody's dead. Dad.
I think that's about as clear as you can get.
How about that drink?
You know
where the bar is.
Hey?
Don't make yourself too comfortable.
Alan's got to sit there.
Alan!
You're lucky you're still breathing.
let alone able to walk.
I suggest you take
full advantage of that fact.
You took
your time.
Where the hell
have you been?
Sit down.
I'll tell you.
So the traffic warden
identified the neighbors' bodies.
which sort of
puts us in the clear.
The only thing connecting
us with the case is those shotguns.
And Tom took
care of them.
SOAP: You did take care of the shotguns.
didn't you. Tom?
I wanted to talk to you
about that.
Well. talk.
Well. actually. no.
I've got them
sitting in the car.
I was gonna sell them
back to Nick the Greek.
but I'm having a bit
of trouble getting hold of him.
You dippy
bastard.
So.
the only thing connecting us
with the case
is in the back of your car.
which is parked outside?
They cost us 700 quid.
I'm not gonna throw them away.
And they're hardly likely to trace
them back to us. are they?
Do you really think
it's worth taking the risk for £700?
Tom. you're a dick.
Now you take those guns.
and you throw them off a bridge.
And throw yourself off
while you're at it.
Now. Tom.
Look. all I'm...
ALL: Now. Tom!
Can I have a beer.
please. Dad?
I'm busy.
Get it yourself.
It seemed Hatchet
underestimated you lot.
and it seems
to have cost him.
Well. I ain't gonna
make the same mistake now. am I?
So I've decided
to bring your bag back.
I think the word you're looking for. gentlemen.
is "thank you".
Thank you.
Now you've presented
me with a problem.
I've lost my employer.
So I've taken care of meself
and me son.
Now if you think
that's unfair.
you come and pay me
a little visit.
But you better
be waving a white flag
high and clear.
so as I can see it.
Or it'll be the last little visit
you ever make.
You understand?
That's all I've
come to say.
There is one
more thing.
It's been emotional.
We are now officially
in the money-lending business.
You all right. Son?
Put your
seat belt on.
We're out of here.
It's empty.
ALL: What's his number?
Don't. don't! You'll jam the line!
I'll call him.
My fucking battery.
Oh. you...
Give me the phone!
No. fuck off! I'll dial it!
Just be calm for a minute.
All right. shut up and tell me the number!
Fuck you!
Give me your phone!
You'll break it! Just calm down!
Give me the phone!
Look. you'll break it.
and it'll be fucked. won't it?
Will you shut?
It's fucking ringing!
(CELL PHONE RINGING)
Watch Online Movies and Series for FREE
www.osdb.link/lm